howtoshout.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy

Every website has owned a privacy policy to tell the visitor that which type of information are collect from the visitor device, location, time, browser and etc. This is the privacy policy page of HowToShout blog read the full page then use the site according to our privacy policy.

## What Information We Collect From Our Visitors (Log Files)

We collect the several information from our visitor who browse our whole website to find his/her content, below is the list of information which includes in the Log file and we collect the below information from our visitors.

  * Page Surfing Time
  * Device
  * Browser
  * Operating System
  * Number Of Pageviews per visitor
  * Number of Sessions per visitor
  * Real Time activity

The above and other information are used by only us we don’t share this information on internet or any other person, your information is use make our site more easy to use, improving our site, to improve visitor service, to improve the visitor experience on our sit, to provide the good content to our visitor and much more.

## We Using Cookies

Cookies are a type of files which are generated from a website which stored on the device of visitors. Here we uses the Cookies on HowToShout to track the visitor is old or new do this we make our site better as possible. If you don’t want to store any cookies on your device then can disable this feature from browser settings.

## We Cannot Share Any user information outside this site

We **cannot** trade, sell or purchase the collected information to the third party websites we do not disclose any information to outside parties so feel free to browse our site.

## Third Party Links

In our few contents we may add some third party links on our website. These third party websites have own independent privacy policies, therefore, we’ve no responsibility for the content and information on these third party linked websites. So before using any third-party sites read their privacy policy page first.

## Having Any Questions regarding this Page

So this is our Privacy Policy page if you have any questions or queries regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our Contact Us Page.

## Changes to HowToShout Privacy Policy

Sometimes we make some changes to this privacy policy, we mention the date that when we make last changes to this privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy was last Modified On 26/04/2016
